#### Contact

Saqr Koryesh, Sheraton Heliopolis +201270727864 (Mobile) oabbas2512@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/oabbas (LinkedIn) tes3awy.netlify.com (Portfolio)

### Top Skills

Web Development
Web Applications
Web Design

### Languages

Arabic (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)
French (Elementary)

### **Publications**

Brain Tumor Detection Based on Object Solidity

# Osama Abbas

Frontend Developer at 34ML

# Summary

Experienced Full Stack Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Communication, Web Development, English, and Arabic. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.) focused on Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering from Arab Academy for Science, Technology and Maritime Transport.

### Experience

34ML

Frontend Developer December 2018 - December 2019 (1 year 1 month) Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Vision Media (VM)
Frontend Developer
June 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 7 months)
Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Vision Media (VM)
Full Stack Developer - JavaScript Developer
June 2017 - December 2018 (1 year 7 months)
Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Experienced in Frontend and Backend technologies.

Arab Academy for Science, Technology and Maritime Transport Part-time Graduate Teaching Assistant September 2016 - June 2017 (10 months)

Cairo Governorate, Egypt

Self-Employed
Personal Tutor
July 2014 - May 2016 (1 year 11 months)
Cairo, Egypt

Preparing lessons for kids, and adults ranging from 10 : 30 years old in English to be able to read, pronounce, and write correctly for being an ESL people.

Estimating through a reward chart to motivate the tutee and obtain a high performance from them.

Rewarding according to the effort exerted through the lessons.

Orange Egypt
Traniee at Orange Academy
April 2016 - April 2016 (1 month)

Arab Academy for Science and Technologyand Maritime Transport, Cairo, Egypt

Traniee

#### **GUPCO**

Telecommunications Traniee
August 2015 - August 2015 (1 month)

Palstine Street, Maadi, Cairo, Egypt

- 1- Learn basic rig components, and different roles of service companies.
- 2- Carry out any work as required by the Team Leader.
- 3- Cultivate and maintain a professional image at all times
- 4- Enforce appropriate Health and Safety procedures and precautions.

#### Qualifications:

- . Bachelor's degree in electronics and communication engineering.
- . Good communication skills.
- . Fluency in written and spoken English.

# Education

Arab Academy for Science, Technology and Maritime Transport Bachelor of Applied Science (B.A.Sc.), Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering · (2011 - 2016)